aota.net 2013-05-03

# Privacy Statement - FutureQuest, Inc.

### FutureQuest, Inc. Privacy Statement

FutureQuest, Inc. provides this privacy statement as a demonstration of our firm commitment to honoring your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for all web sites owned and operated by FutureQuest, Inc. including, but not limited to, [FutureQuest.net](http://www.futurequest.net/ "FutureQuest Home Page"), [Aota.net](http://www.aota.net/ "AOTA Home Page"), [QuestReport.com](http://www.questreport.com/ "QuestReport Home Page"), [Net-Sleuth.com](http://www.net-sleuth.com/), and [QuestAffiliates.com](http://www.questaffiliates.com/ "Quest Affiliates Home Page")

FutureQuest, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected via its web sites. FutureQuest, Inc. will not sell, share, or rent the information that we have collected, in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

FutureQuest may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with its servers and/or for administration of its web sites. IP addresses and user agents are also tracked during form submissions. Information collected is used solely to protect FutureQuest, Inc. and its clients from fraudulent requests. 

Information collected is solely for the use of FutureQuest, Inc. and is not distributed to a third party except in the event that illegal or fraudulent activity is recognized. Only then is information passed on, and only to a Law Enforcement Agency. We will also turn over information to Law Enforcement if subpoenaed. 

**Public Forums**

FutureQuest takes full advantage of the power of public message [forums](http://www.aota.net/forums/) by making [forums](http://www.aota.net/forums/), and at times, other public mediums of communication, available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in this area becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Registration**

Use of the message forums, and other public communication options made available by FutureQuest, Inc., requires that the user first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (such as an email address). FutureQuest uses the registration information to contact the user when needed. The user may also make this information public to the community and the Internet at large. FutureQuest, Inc. will not sell or distribute the information provided during registration. Due to the public nature of the services within those areas, however, information disclosed by the user could become public domain. It is the responsibility of the user to protect his information in a manner that is acceptable to the user. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. For example, by setting a cookie on the FutureQuest Order Forms, the user would not have to re-enter his name and address information more than once, thereby saving time while placing multiple orders. If a user rejects the cookie, he may still use the FutureQuest web sites (with the exception of specific utilities that may require the use of cookies to work correctly), however the user would need to re-enter the optional cookie information upon each return visit. 

**Orders**

The FutureQuest Order Forms request information from users for hosting and various other services offered by FutureQuest, Inc., and at times by other vendors and partners. When placing an order or remitting payment, a user must provide contact information, such as name and address, and possibly financial information, such as credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for processing clients' orders and for billing purposes. If a problem is encountered while processing an order or payment, the contact information is used to notify the client. 

**Sharing**

FutureQuest may share aggregate demographic information with its partners, advertisers, and affiliates. Such data is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

FutureQuest, Inc. partners with other vendors from time to time to provide specific services, such as domain registration or merchant accounts. If a user signs up for services provided by such a third party, FutureQuest may share names or other contact information as necessary, to allow them to provide these services. 

These parties may or may not have their own privacy policies. The client is responsible for reading and agreeing to such privacy statements separately, since the provider of these services is a separate entity. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time FutureQuest, Inc. requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as age and preferences). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the [services](http://www.futurequest.net/Services/ "Services") FutureQuest, Inc. offers and at times aggregate information that does NOT identify individual users may be publicly displayed for marketing and partnership purposes. 

**Security**

FutureQuest, Inc. takes every precaution to protect its users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, the information is protected to the best of our ability both online and off-line. 

When a registration or order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or mailing address), the user has the option of entering that information in an encrypted format with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as the [order form](http://www.futurequest.net/Order/ "Order Form"), the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

All forms available on the FutureQuest web sites, that request sensitive information, offer a secure method of submitting. We encourage all users who are capable of utilizing secure areas to use the secure forms. A link to the secure option can be found on any non-secure forms that request sensitive information. 

While FutureQuest uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline in order to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing or [service representative](http://service.futurequest.net/ "Service Desk")) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

**Domain Search & Whois Utilities**

FutureQuest, Inc. offers various [domain search](https://secure.registerapi.com/order/register/check.php?siteid=1702 "Domain Wizard"), whois, trace route, and ping utilities on our web sites solely as a convenience and troubleshooting tool for our clients and visitors. FutureQuest does not collect any information submitted through these scripts for our personal use or otherwise. 

**Log Files**

FutureQuest, Inc. uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather general demographic information for aggregate use. FutureQuest may from time to time share this aggregate information with others providing it is not able to be linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**

The FutureQuest web sites contain links to other web sites that are not associated with FutureQuest, Inc.. FutureQuest, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other web sites. We encourage all users, when leaving the FutureQuest web sites, to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. The FutureQuest Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by web sites owned and operated by FutureQuest, Inc. 

**Newsletters and Mailing Lists**

FutureQuest, Inc. may make available various [mailing lists and newsletters](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report") pertaining to the services and operations of FutureQuest, Inc. If a user wishes to [subscribe](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report") to any of these options he will be required to submit contact information such as an email address. This information will be used for the sole purpose of sending the mailing to the user and will not be shared or sold. 

**Site and Service Updates**

FutureQuest, Inc. may also send its clients [service announcements and updates](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report"). FutureQuest communicates with its clients to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone (if necessary) however the majority of service announcements will occur via the [public message forums](http://www.aota.net/forums/ "Message Forums") or the [QuestReport Mailing List](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report") which allows users (whether FutureQuest clients or not) to [subscribe or unsubscribe](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report") at will. We strongly recommend [subscribing](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report") to the [QuestReport Mailing List](http://www.questreport.com/ "Quest Report"). Being unsubscribed may cause a FutureQuest Site Owner to miss extremely important service updates. 

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as the zip code), FutureQuest, Inc. will provide a way to correct or update the user's personal data. FutureQuest clients may request that their information be updated by sending the appropriate new information to the [Service Desk](http://service.futurequest.net/ "Service Desk"), found at [http://Service.FutureQuest.net](http://service.futurequest.net/ "Service Desk"), or by sending an email to [Service@FutureQuest.net](mailto:Service@FutureQuest.net). 

Canceling: If you need to cancel an account with FutureQuest, Inc., you must use the cancellation form provided at [http://www.FutureQuest.net/Billing/Cancel/](http://www.futurequest.net/Billing/Cancel/ "Cancel Service")

 **Notification of Changes**

If there are changes to the FutureQuest Privacy Policy, FutureQuest will post those changes on the web site so its users are always aware of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point FutureQuest plans to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, users will be notified by way of an email. Users will be given a reasonable amount of time to choose whether or not FutureQuest may use their information in this different manner. 

**Children**

FutureQuest, Inc. does not target any of our services towards children, but if there happens to be a child under the age of 13 that chooses to sign up for our service we will not knowingly: 

  * Collect online contact information from a child under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent or direct parental notification of the nature and intended use of this information, which shall include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Where prior verifiable parental consent is not obtained, online contact information shall only be used to directly respond to the child's request and shall not be used to re-contact the child for other purposes.
  * Collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.
  * Distribute to any third party any personally identifiable information collected from a child under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.
  * Give the ability to children under 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior verifiable parental consent, and will make best efforts to prohibit a child from posting any contact information. 
  * Entice a child under 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in such activity. 

If a parent or guardian wishes to provide permission for their child to use the services offered by FutureQuest, Inc, visit [http://www.FutureQuest.net/About/Privacy/Consent.php](http://www.futurequest.net/About/Privacy/Consent.php "Privacy Parental Consent Form") to complete, print, sign, and FAX the permission form. 

If a parent or guardian wishes to close a child's account, please let us know by visiting the cancellation form provided at [http://www.FutureQuest.net/Billing/Cancel/](http://www.futurequest.net/Billing/Cancel/ "Cancel Account")

For more information or to contact a FutureQuest Representative visit the FutureQuest [Service Desk](http://service.futurequest.net/ "Service Desk") at [http://Service.FutureQuest.net](http://service.futurequest.net/ "Service Desk") or send email to [Service@FutureQuest.net](mailto:Service@FutureQuest.net)

* * *

FutureQuest Site Search 

Loading

Back to Top
